Assignment 1 readme.txtQuestion 1: File, ca/mcgill/ecse202/a1/Question1.java. To run simply call “java Question1.java”. It will output the students names and IDs to the console.Question 2: File, ca/mcgill/ecse202/a1/Question2.java. To run simply call “java Question2.java”. User will be prompted to enter width and height of a rectangle. It will output the perimeter, area, and diagonal length of the rectangle.
Question 3: File, ca/mcgill/ecse202/a1/Question3.java. To run simply call “java Question3.java”. User will be prompted to enter the coordinates of two points (x1, y1) and (x2, y2). It will display the slope of the line connects the two points.
Question 4: File, ca/mcgill/ecse202/a1/Question4.java. To run simply call “java Question4.java”. User will be prompted to enter the coordinates of two points (x1, y1) and (x2, y2). It will display the line equation in the slope-intercept form (it won't display m if it is 1 or b if it is 0).